Guide to the Division of Academic Affairs Records RG 6
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 9. Course Materials
  - School of Arts and Sciences
    - Miscellaneous, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Humanistic Studies, ca. 1975-2002 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      Materials include course descriptions and proposals to change courses.
    - Arabic, 2005-2013 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - German, 1971-2013 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Hebrew101-102, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Italian, 1980-2013 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Chinese 162-164, 2010-2013 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      Materials include proposals to add new courses.
    - Latin 122-157, 1965-2006 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      Materials include course descriptions and proposals to delete courses.
    - Portuguese 150-197, 1978-2013 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Non-Western Cultures, 1989-2000 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - French 150-170, 1976-2013 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - French, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Communication and Theatre Arts 115-296, 1973-2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Communications and Theatre Arts 315-402, 1976-2004 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Math 098-118, 1989-2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Math 120-150, 1979-2011 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Math 165-198, 2002-2013 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Materials include course descriptions and proposals for modifications to courses.
    - Math 211-282, 1979-2011 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Math 301-347, 1975-2011 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Math 350-383, 1969-2011 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Math 400-482, 1969-2011 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Materials include course descriptions, proposals to delete courses, and proposals to modify courses.
    - Math Majors/Minors, 1999-2006 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Spanish 101-157, 1976-2010 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Materials include course descriptions and proposals to modify curriculum.
    - Spanish 161-197, 1976-2013 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Materials include course descriptons and proposals to modify courses.
    - Spanish 201-221, 1975-2008 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Spanish 224-283, 1976-2007 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Spanish 300-337, 1975-2007 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Materals include course descriptions and proposals to modify courses.
    - Spanish 340-375, 1976-2007 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Materials include course descriptions and proposals to modfy courses.
    - Spanish 385-448, 2004-2007 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Spanish Major/Minor, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - English 098-107, 1969-2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - English 119-139, 1977-2007 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - English 140-161, 1969-2004 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - English 200-2008, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - English 209-219, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - English 220-228, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - English 231-259, 1969-2004 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - English 260-298, 1979-2007 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - English 302-308, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - English 310-319, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      Materials include proposals for course modifications, deletions and course outlines.
    - English 320-339, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      Materials include proposals for course modificiations, deletions and course descriptions.
    - English 340-360, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      Materials include proposals for course modifications, deletions, additions and course outlines.
    - English 372-391, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - English 420-425, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      Materials include proposals for course modifications, additions, deletions, and course outlines.
    - English 426-446, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      Materials include proposals for course modifications, deletions and additions, and course outlines.
    - English 450-490, 1969-2007 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      Materials include proposals for modification, deletion, addition and course outlines.
    - English Majors/Minors, 1997-2007 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      Materials include proposals for modification and addition to English majors and minors.
    - Afro-American Studies 100-233, 1975-2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Materials include proposals to modify courses and course outlines.
    - Afro-American Studies 251-350, 1975-2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Studies 217-400, Majors/Minors, 1975-2009 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Anthropology 100-222, 1969-2008 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Materials include proposals to add and modify courses, and course outlines.
    - Anthropology 255-305, 1970-2008 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Anthropology 311-400, 1970-2008 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Materials include proposals to modify courses and course descriptions.
    - Astronomy 122-405, 1970-2009 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Materials include proposals for course modifications and course outlines.
    - Basic Studies 100-137, 1974-1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Chemistry 100-250, 1969-2012 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Materials include proposals to modify and add new classe and course outlines.
    - Chemistry 301-442, 1969-2008 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Communications 110-212, 1969-2012 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Materials include proposals to modify courses and course outlines
    - Communications 215-264, 1969-2011 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Communications 266-299, 1970-2013 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Communications 300-394, 1970-2013 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Communications 402-444, 1978-2010 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Communications 446-495, 1990-2010 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Communications Majors/Minors, 1997-2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Computer Science Minor, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Materials include proposals for minors in computer science.
    - Cotnract Majors, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
      Materials include proposals for students to obtain degrees not offered at WCSU based on specific coursework.
    - Environmental Science 100-442, 1975-2011 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Geography 100-290, 1969-2012 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Geology 100-410, 1968-1999 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Honors Bachelors Degree, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Materials include form for interdisciplary honors degree.
    - Honors Courses, 1988-2010 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Meteorology 150-490 and Majors/Minors, 1997-2012 (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
      Materials include proposals to modfiy courses and course outlines.
    - Women's Studies 200-286, 1996-2008 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - World Languages and Literature, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Computer Science 104-245, 1989-2011 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Computer science 250-356, 1982-2008 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Computer Science 358-484 and Majors/Minors, 1989-2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Psychology 100-201, 1979-2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Psychology 203-225, 1979-2006 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Psychology 230-246, 1979-2009 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Psychology 252-294 and Majors/Minors, 1979-2006 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Biology 100-124, 1969-2010 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Biology 125-204, 1966-2007 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Biology 205-225, 1967-2007 (Box 14, Frame 9)
    - Biology 252-330, 1969-2007 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Biology 360-475, 1973-2011 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Biology Majors/Minors, 1970-2009 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - History 101-210, 1972-2013 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - History 211-228, 1976-2011 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - History 231-270, 1975-2011 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - History 271-292, 1979-2011 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - History 293-319, 1976-2011 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - History 320-368, 1976-2008 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - History 380-490 and Majors/Minors, 1989-2013 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Writing 098-244, 2007-2009 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Writing 245-340, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Writing 342-490 and language 317-320, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Writing Majors/Minors, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Social Science 1980-2011 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Social Science Majors/Minors, 2000-2006 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Sociology 100-225, 1969-2012 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Sociology 230-441, 1976-2008 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Economics 100-220, 1969-1997 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Economics 230-448 and Majors/Minors, 1969-2012 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Philosophy100-340, 1989-2013 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Medical Technology 302 and Major, 1977-2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Materials include proposal to modify program and course descriptions.
    - Astronomy, 1996-2012 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Physics 101-140, 1972-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Physics 150-490, 1973-2007 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Political Science 100-217, 1969-2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Political Science 237-403, 1976-2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Psychology 203-425, 1979-2012 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Psychology 432-476, 1979-2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - School of Professional Studies
    - Education 206-235, 1979-2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      Materials include proposals to modify courses and course materials.
    - Education 297-340, 1976-2005 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Education Majors/Minors, 1990-2006 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      Materials include proposals to modify majors/minors and course track materials.
    - Education 351-411, 1968-2006 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Education 412-460, 1944-2010 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Education Psychology 200-405, 1970-2010 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Health Education, 1960-2006 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Community Health 100-293, 1990-2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Community Health 310-491, 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Health Promotion and Exercise 100-281, 2002-2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Health Promotion and Exercise 310-491, 2003-2012 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Health Promotion and Exercise Majors/Minors, 2003-2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Nursing 100-218, 1993-2012 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Nursing 220-304, 1996-2012 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nursing 309-336, 1976-2012 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Nursing 350-376, 1979-2012 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Nursing Program, 1999-2009 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Materials include proposals to modify the program and program materials.
    - Physical Education 131-181, 1980-2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Social Work 100-245, 1979-2013 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Social Work 250-306, 1988-2013 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Social Work 309-315, 1978-2012 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Social Work 316-350, 1996-2012 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - School of Performing Arts
    - Art 100-222, 1971-2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Art 225-314, 1980-2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Art 322-370 and Majors/Minors, 1969-2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Music 100-196, 1976-2012 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Music 208-335, 1976-2012 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Music 340-397 and Majors/Minors, 1997-2012 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Music Education 100-304, 1977-2006 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Music Education 316-380 and Majors/minors, 1980-2008 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Materials include proposals to change courses and programs and course descriptions.
    - Theatre 125-260, 1969-2013 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Theatre 279-386, 1969-2013 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Theatre 387-490 and Majors/minors, 1969-2013 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous Materials from all four schools, 1969-2006 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      Materials include: Ancell: Change undecided/undeclared to exploratory studies Change Faculty developed study to Faculty developed course Change Student developed study to Student independent study VPA: Change Undecided/undeclared to Exploratory Studies Change Faculty developed study to Faculty developed course Change Student developed study to Student independent study Modify Theater Arts program SPT 265 SPT/AV 140 Revision of Human Relations option program Arts and Science: Change Faculty developed study to Faculty developed course Change Student developed study to Student independent study Change Undecided/undeclared to Exploratory Studies Professional Studies: Change Faculty developed study to Faculty developed course Change Student developed study to Student independent study Change Undecided/undeclared to Exploratory Studies Methods of Instruction in Foreign Languages for the Classroom